telekothon.com 2018-03-11

# Privacy Policy - telekothon.com

This website is owned and operated by TeleKothon Team . We are committed to safeguarding the privacy of our website visitors, this policy sets out how we will treat your personal information.

The Privacy Policy applies to all Visitors and Users (collectively referred to as "Users"). In addition, this Privacy Policy applies to all contents provided by this site. This Privacy Policy describes how we handle your information for our services on the websites. It applies generally to the website and content and other related websites where this Policy appears in the footer of the page.

TeleKothon.com takes privacy issues very seriously. We use demographic and traffic information of our users only to analyze the readers community. This does not include personal reader information. Submission of this information on TeleKothon.com is always optional and will never be provided to 3rd parties.

**• Personal information  Security :**

TeleKothon does not collect user personal identification information automatically. User personal information ( e.g., your name, e-mail address and message ) is collected only when user voluntarily submit through our contact us form. We may reply to user via email in return of their messages. However, we collect these information to enhance user experience.

**• Use of Personal Information :**

We don't sell or rent your personal information to third parties for their marketing purposes without your explicit consent.  If you don't wish to receive marketing communications from us , please contact from this page [ **[Contact Us](http://www.telekothon.com/p/contact.html) **].

**• Using Information from[www.telekothon.com](http://www.telekothon.com/) :**

[www.telekothon.com](http://www.telekothon.com/) enables you to share personal and financial information to complete different activities. We encourage you to disclose your privacy practices and respect the privacy of other users. Though, we guarantee the privacy or security of your information but always suggest you to be updated by yourself on the privacy and security policies of this website and its affiliated sites before entering into a transaction and choosing to share your information.

**•  General : **

We will try to provide you with adequate information so you can make an informed decision whether to visit these website.

Subject to the requirements of applicable law, we strive to provide a consistent set of privacy practices throughout the website trading community. By accepting the Privacy Policy and the Terms & Conditions , you expressly consent to our collection, storage, use and disclosure of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy.

**• Message for users :**

This Privacy Policy is effective upon acceptance for new users and is otherwise effective from November 01 , 2013. This Privacy Policy should be read in conjunction with the terms and conditions of this website. If you have any question about our privacy policy please contact from this page [ [**Contact Us**](http://www.telekothon.com/p/contact.html) ].

**•  We will be glad to hear from you if:**

\- You have found a mistake in our contents.  
\- You have info about any contents which we don't have in our database.  
\- You have found a broken link.  
\- You have a suggestion for improving TeleKothon.com or you want to request a feature.

**•  Before [Contact Us](http://www.telekothon.com/p/contact.html) us an email, please keep in mind :**

\- We do not sell email addresses  
\- We don't answer any "Which mobile operator OR Wimax may I use?" questions.

**•  ** **COPYRIGHT INFORMATION**

Copyright © 2012-2013 TeleKothon.com All Rights Reserved. Some company and Contents  names on this site may be trademarks or registered trademarks of individual companies and are respectfully acknowledged.
